

# **SERGIO MONJARAZ**

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

- @ mta.sergio.monjaraz@gmail.com
- in in/sergio-monjaraz-ramirez/
- **(+52)4431090731**
- Morelia, Mich. Mexico

## **STRENGTHS**

React JS

Angular

Vue

HTML5

TS/JS CSS/SASS

NodeJS GIT

SOLID )

Clean Code

CI/CD

AWS Azure

Jira SCRUM

### **LEARNING**

Docker

Kubernetes

Django

Mongo DB

GraphQL

Machine learning

**Computer Vision** 

## **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native

**English: Medium** 

#### **ABOUT ME**

Computer systems engineer with 7 + years of experience developing web applications using javascript (React, Vue and Angular) and services(REST). My passion is technology and my objective is develop software solutions along with highly performance and dynamic teams. I consider myself a proactive and autodidact person with ease to learn new things and i like the challenges.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Front-End Developer | Top Doctors/BeHIT

**August 2024 - Current** 

- Remote
- Implementation and migration of platform for hospital management, the project was done on angular 1 and was migrated to vue 3, using MEVN (Mongo, Express, Vue, Node) stack

#### Front-End Developer | Blueyonder

- **i** April 2022 August 2024
- Remote
- Developing a custom React component library for application teams that delivers high performance and custom functionality for the company.

#### Front-End Developer | Citelis

- **=** February 2021 March 2022
- Morelia, Mich., Mexico
- Implementation of a CRM for Jac Mexico (a partner brand) that help to improve his process of the sales and the tracking for each client also to providing data that helps decision making.

#### Front-End Developer | Securitec

- **August 2021 June 2022**
- Remote/Freelance
- Developed a system omnichannel for customer service, using vue 3, and WebRTC, this system is on the cloud and offerts a high customization.

#### Full-Stack Developer | Kiritek

- February 2019 February 2021
- Morelia, Mich., Mexico
- Developed and improved processes for MyFrac Project using Vue 2, AWS and Java. That helped to grow project and improved sales of 100% in new neighborhoods.

Contributed to design a mobile app to e-signature to help users to signature docs from mobile devices

### **EDUCATION**

### Master's degree in Advance Technology | Instituto Politecnico Nacional

- **a** August 2015 August 2017
- Queretaro, Queretaro
- Research award 2019 from Instituto Politecnico Nacional for the project counting pedestrians with a zenithal arrangement of depth cameras.

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering | Instituto Tecnologico de Morelia

**=** February 2010 - August 2015

Morelia, Mich